本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
嘿  老爸  我想报名参加冰球队
Hey, dad, I want to sign up for hockey.
-不  你才没呢  -我想
-No, you don't. -Yeah, I do.
不  你不想  小点声
No, you don't! Keep your voice down.
怎么了  对冰球有意见吗
Why? What's wrong with hockey?
嘘  嘘  嘘
Shh shh shh!
我听到有人说冰球了
Did someone say hockey?
没有啊  亲爱的
N-no, honey.
我说我感觉自己有点像
I said I was feeling a little...
肉球
Stocky.
我从通风口听到了有人说冰球
I heard the word hockey come up from the air vent.
我就想问问能打冰球吗  然后老爸就开始抓狂了
I asked if I could play hockey and then dad got all weird.
我朝思暮想的能有一天
I have been dreaming of the day.
我能有个孩子可以穿上冰鞋
When one of my kids strapped on the skates.
然后跟随我的脚步一直走下去
And followed in mama's footsteps.
-又要讲故事了  -我曾经是
-I feel a story coming on. -I was the star.
丹佛西南社区大学女子冰球队的一颗耀眼明星
Of the southwest Denver community college lady icers.
-甚至还有个可爱的外号  -他们叫我“疯子”
-You even had a cute nickname. -They called me "psycho."
成功的打破了联赛罚时记录
Broke the league record for penalty minutes.
-这就是为什么他们叫我  -疯子  晓得了
-And that's why they called me... -Psycho. I got it.
那我能打冰球吗
Can I play hockey?
你不仅可以打冰球
Not only can you play hockey,
我还要把我在体育方面的毕生所学传授于你
I'm gonna teach you everything I know about the sport.
我倍感荣幸  但还是算了  人家有教练的
No, that's okay, mom. They actually have coaches.
教练  我来当你教练如何
Coach... I'll be your coach!
-这主意太好了  -疯子教练
-Great idea! - Coach psycho.
-疯子  -没错  查莉
-Psycho. -That's right, Charlie.
老娘我是疯子
Mommy's psycho.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  sarina
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十二集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E012  The Break Up
-好了  明天见  宝贝  -好的
-Okay, see you tomorrow, babe. -Okay.
噢  对了  德里克
Oh, hey, Derek,
我想问问放学后
I was wondering if maybe after school.
-你想去打迷你高尔夫吗  -嗯  随便了
-You wanna go mini golfing? -Eh, whatever.
好吧  那么这个随便了是代表着
Okay, so, um, is that a whatever like...
“我不想去”  还是代表着
"I don't wanna go," or a whatever like
“迷你高尔夫  我来也”
"mini golf, wow!"?
无所谓了
Whichever.
好吧  那么这个无所谓了是代表着“随便了”
Okay okay, so is that a whichever like "whatever"
还是代表着“迷你高尔夫  我来也”
Or a whichever like "mini golf, wow!"?
-别纠结了  -爱咋咋地吧
-No worries. -Whatever.
-好了  再见了  -再见
-'kay, see you, babe. -Okay.
艾薇  我能问你点儿事吗
Ivy, can I ask you something?
-可以  问吧  -是关于德里克的
-Sure, what's up? -It's about Derek.
我要你实话实说
And I want you to be completely honest.
你也知道  我们交往也有一段时间了
You know, we've been going out for a while.
起初每件事都是那么的美好  但现在
And at first it was fun and everything, but now
我在考虑是不是应该
I'm kinda wondering if maybe I should...
甩了这个大白痴
Dump his sorry butt!
-哇  -现在就甩
-Whoa. -Do it! Now.
他可能还在外面的  俺去把他拽回来
He's probably still out there. I'll go get him.
哇  艾薇  艾薇  别急
Whoa, Ivy, Ivy, wait!
我并不是说现在去甩他
I don't mean right now.
我还没有甩人的经验  而且我还有点紧张
I've never broken up with somebody before and I'm kind of nervous about it.
-这有啥紧张的  -我也不知道啊
-There's nothing to be nervous about. -Well, I... I don't know.
这很简单的  听着
It's easy. Look.
把我想成德里克  然后和我分手
Just pretend I'm Derek and break up with me.
俺可以扮演德里克的
If it helps,
只要摆出一张臭脸  然后用嘴呼吸
I'll put a stupid look on my face and breathe through my mouth.
算了  我才不要练习和某人分手呢
No, I'm not gonna practice breaking up with somebody.
我是说  这能难于上青天吗
I mean, how hard can it be?
我只要告诉德里克我的感受  友好的
I just tell Derek how I feel... nicely...
然后我们就开始过自己的生活了
And then we both go on with our lives.
呵呵  无所谓了
Heh heh. Whatever.
成了  能别再整这套了吗
Okay, could you stop doing that, please?
啊  俺喜欢
Ehhh, I like it.
好轻松啊  俺感觉俺的大脑在度假呢
It's relaxing. I feel like my brain's on vacation.
好了  同志们  听好了
Okay, people, listen up.
公司里的精英们又想出了一道新美食
The geniuses at corporate have come up with a new menu item.
他们取名为麦香鸡肉末
They are called chicken slivers.
-什么叫鸡肉末  是块状的吗  -不是
-What's a sliver? Is it like a nugget? -No.
-那它鲜嫩多汁吗  -不
-Is it like a tender? -Nope.
-那它里面有鸡肉吗  -从法律上讲
-Does it have chicken in it? -According to legal,
这个回答应该是“可能”
The answer to that question is "possibly."
你们记住  这不仅是麦香鸡肉末
And remember, they're not just chicken slivers,
它们是咕唧下士的麦香鸡肉末
They are corporal kwikki's chicken slivers,
为纪念我们的创始人  布尔·咕唧下士
In honor of our founder, corporal bull s. Kwikki.
-他是什么的下士  -吧唧嘴
-What's he a corporal of? -Lip-smacking goodness.
这也是他自传的题目
Which is also the title of his autobiography.
好了  苦工们  发薪水了
Okay, minimum wagers... paychecks.
-谢谢  -谢谢
-Thanks. -Thank you.
米奇  难道我们就只能得到最少的薪酬吗
Mitch, aren't we supposed to be making minimum wage?
我们有法律保障的  我爸告诉我的
It's the law. My dad told me about it.
千万别和你们的家长说
Never talk to your parents!
说真的  同志们  这里是如此的神圣
Seriously, guys, what happens here is sacred.
是一个没有父母的港湾
This is a safe place.
等一下  “最少”也就是至少
Wait a minute. "minimum" means the least.
难道我们挣的比至少还少
We're making less than the least?
好了  开业了
Okay, doors opening,
让我们一起喂饱这个世界吧
Let's feed the world, huh?
你有什么办法能拯救我们这些苦工吗
Isn't there something you can do about our salary?
-为什么是我  -你是这里最聪明的一个
-Why me? -You're the smartest one here.
是吗
I am?
但我的脚困在拖把水桶里了
But my foot's in a mop bucket.
是啊  但你知道如何转危为安
Yeah, but you know how to get it out.
我还以为要去滑冰场呢
I thought we were going to the ice rink.
不去  直到你先学会了基本功我们再去溜冰场
No. You can't go anywhere near the ice until you learn the fundamentals.
感觉好无聊啊
Sounds boring.
一点儿都不无聊  有趣极了
It's not boring. It's fun!
你看  基本功里怎么能少得了“乐趣”
Come on, you can't spell fundamental without "fun."
基本功里也同样少不了“疯狂”
You also can't spell it without "mental."
别贫了  基本功第一条  防守
Okay, fundamental number one: Positioning.
怎么有个垫子靠墙上了
Why is there a pad on the wall?
因为我要保证安全第一
Because I believe in safety first.
-搞什么  -搞的是阻挡
-What was that? -That's called checking.
在你们这个等级的比赛中是违规的
It's not allowed at your level...
除非裁判没有看见你
Unless the ref doesn't see you.
-现在你来撞我  -不可能  你可是我亲娘
-Now you check me. -No way, you're my mom.
少装了  来撞我  你这个胆小鬼
Come on, check me, you little weenie.
这招叫躲闪
That's called avoiding a check.
快起来  来练习下滑冰
Get up. Let's practice your skating.
看着  我先给你示范下
Okay, I will demonstrate.
到位而轻松  就像老娘我
Nice and easy, just like mama.
-你来试试  -好吧
-Now you try. -Okay.
-不赖嘛  -只是不赖吗
-Not bad. -Not bad?
我觉着我很在行啊
I'd say I'm pretty good.
不要放松警惕
Never get comfortable.
-嘿  我的小可爱  -嘿  老爸
-Hey, sweetie pie. -Hey, dad.
其实我是在
Actually I was...
嘿  PJ
Hey, P.J.
-你没事吧  -工作中遇到困难了
-You okay?  I got a big problem at work.
我发现我老板少付工资给我们
I found out my boss is underpaying us.
现在职工们想让我找出解决问题的办法
And now the staff wants me to do something about it.
-为什么选你  -我是最聪明的
-Why you? -I'm the smartest.
呃  怎么评出来的
Um... How exactly was that determined?
不知道  可能是不记名投票
I don't know. Probably a secret vote.
也可能是抽签
Maybe a raffle.
好吧  那你打算怎么办
Uh, well, what are you gonna do?
不知道呢
I don't know.
-无计可施啊  -PJ
-I don't know. -P.J.!
在你一生中  你不能一遇到问题就说“不知道”
You can't go through life answering every question with "I don't know."
是吗
Really?
怎么就一生了  目前我还只是一个高三的学生
I have so far and I'm a senior in High School.
应该就是抽签了
Probably a raffle.
呃  听着
Um, look,
儿子  如果你认为理应得到更多的钱
Son, if you think you deserve more money,
那你就站出来为自己辩护
Then stand up for yourself.
不要忘了  你的同事们  正在指望着你
By the way, your coworkers, they are counting on <i>you</i>
变得更强
To be strong.
老天爷啊  我刚发现我是聪明的
Oh man, I just found out I'm smart,
难道我现在还要变得更强吗
Now I have to be strong too?
享受你童年的每一刻吧  查莉  迟早会长大的
Enjoy your childhood, Charlie. It does not last forever.
吃饼干吗
Cookie?
PJ想吃饼干
P.J. Wuv a cookie.
好了  好了  他在这里呢
Okay... Okay okay, he's here.
噢  艾薇  我对这事心里没底啊
Oh, Ivy, I don't know if I can do this.
我的心怦怦直跳  噢  嗨  他看见我了
My heart is pounding. Oh, hi, he sees me!
他在招手  好了  现在我也招手  面带微笑
He's waving. All right, now I'm waving and smiling.
感觉不对劲啊  先挂了
This feels so wrong. Gotta go.
-好啊  德里克  -嘿
-Hey there, hi, Derek. -Hey.
好啊  感谢前来和我见面
Oh hi, thank you for meeting me.
-嘿  没事的  -好的  啊
-Hey, no worries. -Yeah, uh...
听着  这可能有点
Well, there might be a few.
听着  我欠一个道歉
Listen, I owe you an apology.
-为什么道歉  -为了推掉迷你高尔夫球那件事
-For what? -For blowing off that whole mini golf thing.
噢  不用  不用  没关系的
Oh no no no, that's okay.
不  有关系的  因为你是我的女朋友
No! No, it's not. You're my girl.
我应该学会爱屋及乌
If you like mini golf, I should like mini golf.
我也不是那么喜欢迷你高尔夫  既然说到
I don't like mini golf that much. And speaking of.
-不喜欢的事  -等一下
-Not liking things... - Wait.
在你说之前  我有些东西要给你
Before you say anything else, I've got something for you.
噢  天啊
Oh, ha ha.
像你一样的皮夹克
A leather jacket just like yours.
没错  除了这件上面有“德的女友”
Yeah, except this one says "d's girl."
喜欢吗
You like it?
有什么不喜欢的呢  我是说
What's not to like? I mean, I...
我既然是德的女友  那在皮夹克
I'm d's girl, now it says so...
上写出来又有什么关系
On a jacket.
-是啊  没错  穿上试试  -好吧
-Yeah, well, try it on. -Ooo-kay.
哇  太棒了
Wow, awesome.
现在当你坐在我摩托车后座上时
Now when you're on the back of my bike.
大家都会知道你是谁了
Everyone will know who you are.
我是德的女友
D's girl.
-怎么了  -米奇  我们需要谈谈
-What's going on? -Mitch, we need to talk.
你知道鸡肉里是什么了
You found out what's in the chicken?
-不是  -你知道我们拿什么喂鸡了
-No. -You found out what we feed the chickens?
-不是  -是不是你在吮指鸡套餐里头发现了手指
-No. -Is this about the finger in the fingers?
-什么  -为什么你不直接
-What?! -Why don't you.
告诉我到底是什么事
Tell me what this is about?
-我们要求涨薪  -涨薪是吧
-We want a raise. -A raise.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
我们可以在你下次薪资协商中讨论下
We can discuss that at your next salary negotiation.
我认为协商会安排在
Which I believe is scheduled for the 5th of...
猴年马月
Octembruary.
那根本就不是一个确定的日期
That's not even a real month!
我说的没错吧  PJ
Right, P.J.?
听着  米奇  你现在的行为很不厚道
Look, Mitch, what you're doing is wrong.
而我们是不会让你得逞的
And we're not gonna let you get away with it.
-我们要求涨薪  -要是我偏不涨呢
-We demand a raise! -And if I don't give it to you.
那你奈我何  举行罢工吗
You're gonna what? Go on strike?
-你还真说对了  -你打算就这么走出去
-That's exactly what we'll do. -You're gonna walk right out?
如果罢工需要走出去  那我就走
If that's what striking is, then yes.
好吧
All right.
就这么定了
开始罢工了  同志们
Come on, guys.
-你会后悔的  -我们不会的
-You'll be sorry. -No, we won't.
呃  我有点后悔了
Uh, I'm kinda sorry.
我把钱包落在休息室了
I left my wallet in the break room.
听好了  大家  我们罢工了
All right, guys, we're on strike.
耶
Yeah!
那我们现在干嘛
What do we do now?
我也不知道
I don't know.
在我们想什么是罢工的同时
While we figure out what a strike is,
不如先让开路  便于让顾客们进来
Let's get out of the way and let the customers in.
-欢迎光临咕唧炸鸡  -尝尝麦香鸡肉末
-Welcome to kwikki chikki. -Try the slivers!
妈  妈  嗨
Mom, mom, hi.
-泰迪  你来干嘛  -我需要你的建议
-Teddy, what are you doing here? -I need some advice.
噢  亲爱的  我在工作呢
Oh honey, I'm working.
知道  但这是关于我的感情生活
Yeah, but this is about my love life.
噢  宝贝  等到晚上再说吧
Oh honey, I think that can wait till tonight.
邓肯护士  三一二房的病人需要洗澡了
<i>Nurse Duncan, patient in 312</i> <i>needs a sponge bath.</i>
朗达  你能给那位病人去洗澡吗
Rhonda, can you handle that?
我正在解决家庭危机呢
I'm dealing with a family crisis right here.
谢谢了
Thank you.
啥事  说吧
What up, girl?
就是这事
This is what's up.
德的女友  我还以为你要和德里克分手呢
D's girl? I thought you were gonna break up with Derek?
没错  我试过  但他却给了我件夹克
Yeah, I tried, but then he gave me this jacket.
现在我不知所措了
And now I don't know what to do.
宝贝  这种事并非易事  你越往后拖
Honey, these things are never easy, but the longer.
事情就会越糟糕
You let it go on the worse it's gonna be.
好了  向自己保证
Okay, just promise yourself.
下次见到德里克后  必须要和他分手
The very next time you see Derek, you're gonna break up with him.
好吧
Okay.
好的  好的  下次就分
Okay okay, the very next time.
-好的  -嘿
-Yes. -Hey!
噢嘿  德里克  搞什么  德里克
Oh hey, Derek. What... Derek?!
-老天爷啊  -你怎么了
-Oh my gosh. -What happened?
呃  是这样的  我当时在骑摩托车
Uh, well, I was on my motorcycle.
当我骑到那间卖泰迪熊的商店时
And then I passed that store that sells Teddy bears.
我就想到了你  毕竟你就是我的泰迪熊嘛
And I started thinking of you 'cause, well, you're my Teddy bear.
再然后我就骑进了某人的后院
And then I was in someone's backyard.
这次就算了
Not t<i>very</i> next time.
不给钱  就罢工
No bucks, no clucks.
你要想从此过
Are you really gonna cross this picket line?
就先过了她这关
You're gonna have to go through her.
好耶
Yeah!
我喊“咕唧”  你们喊“垃圾”
I say "chikki," you say "icky."
-咕唧  咕唧  -垃圾  垃圾
-Chikki chikki! -Icky icky!
情况如何啊  罢工者
How's it going out here, strikers?
米奇  你是来妥协我们所提出的条件的吗
So, Mitch, are you here to meet our demands?
不是  我是来接见我的新雇员的
No. I'm here to meet my new employees.
欢迎入驻咕唧炸鸡店  马上开工了
Welcome to kwikki chikki. Let's get started right away.
好了  别在乎是不是洗过手了
All right, don't worry about washing your hands.
我们怎么办
What about us?
噢  告诉你们个好消息  全被炒鱿鱼了
Oh, good news. You're all fired.
-这不公平  -和那个天才说去
-That's not fair. -Tell that to the genius.
那个让你们罢工的人
That told you to go out on strike.
多谢你了  PJ
Thanks a lot, P.J.
怎么  同志们
Wha... guys?
还没结束呢  同志们  回来啊
This isn't over. Guys, come back!
好了  看样子就剩咱俩了  查莉
Well, it looks like it's just you and me, Charlie.
我不知道你要去哪
I don't know where you're going.
你可是我载过来的
I'm your ride!
老妈  快点
Mom, come on!
来吧  菜鸟  让我看看你的能耐
Come on, rookie, let's see what you got.
这就是我的能耐
This is what I got.
都是冰球惹的祸
Had to play hockey.
盖比  宝贝  如果你还想踏入冰场
Gabe, honey, you're gonna have to do better than that.
就必须要做到更好
If you ever want to set foot on the ice.
好了  继续
Okay, bring it.
这下好了  老爸
Well, dad,
我听从了你的意见  为自己辩护
I took your advice, made a stand.
嘿  干得好  然后呢
Hey, good for you. And?
大家统统被炒鱿鱼
Everyone got fired.
-这下悲剧了  -是啊
-That's terrible. -Yeah.
-这还用说  -真的很抱歉
-I know. -I'm really sorry.
我感觉我对此事有不可推卸的责任
I... I-I can't help feeling kind of responsible for all this.
没错  你是要负责的  所以你的感觉是对的
Well, you are responsible, so your feeling is correct.
听着  肯定有人可以帮你去平反的
Look, there's gotta be somebody you can talk to.
-去找你老板的领导  -谁啊
-Go over your boss's head. -To who?
就算找布尔·咕唧下士也无济于事
Not even corporal bull s. Kwikki himself could save us now.
广告里的那个家伙
The guy in the ads?
真有其人
He's real?
是啊  当然是真有其人了
Yeah, of course he's real.
他的那匹马真叫“油炸卷”吗
And he really has a horse named "curly fry"?
那只是广告里的玩笑
That was a joke in a commercial.
你连自己的过去都不知道吗
You don't even know your history.
好了
Okay.
-准备好了吗  -准备好了
-You ready? -Yeah, I'm ready.
好了  径直走去
All right, just get in there,
伤他的心  径直走出
Break his heart and get out.
-嘿  -嘿
-Hey. -<i>Hey.</i>
-想坐下吗  -呃  算了  算了
-Are you gonna sit down? -Uh, no. No, um...
我想和你说点儿事  我要说了
There's something I want to say. I'm just gonna say it.
这可能有点痛苦  因为我知道你迷恋姐
This might be a little tough because I know you're into me.
你还给了我件夹克  但是
You got me that jacket, but, uh,
我想说的是
The thing is...
我觉着咱们应该分手
I think we should break up.
呃  没问题
Uh... Okay.
没问题
Okay?
是啊  我是说  如果你希望如此
Yeah, I mean, if... if it's what you want.
是啊  那就是我希望的
Yeah, no, that's what I want.
不用担心了
No worries.
太好了
Great.
好了  那就
Okay, well...
-再见  -拜
-Goodbye. -Bye.
好了  对不起
Okay, sorry,
看来你应付这事挺得心应手的啊  为什么呢
You're taking this really well. Why is that?
我是说  那个  如果
I mean, well, if it's not working...
分手这事让我伤心欲绝  反而让你轻松快活  对吧
It wasn't working for me, but it was working for you, right?
是的  无所谓了
Sure. Whatever.
你厉害  再一次和你
Cool. Goodbye.
再见
Again.
好了  对不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
我来是让你伤心欲绝的  而你这么优雅的反映
I'm breaking your heart here. The polite response.
总该给我流露出点儿感情吧
Would be to show a little bit of emotion!
-嘿  俺们此行的目的是什么  -我太不爽了
-Hey, how are we doing over here? -Not so great!
我刚和德里克分手了  但他应付得相当自如
I just broke up with Derek and he's taking it really well!
-这不是好事吗  -不是
-But that's good, right? -No!
不是  我要让他伤心欲绝
No no, I want him to be devastated.
你为什么不伤心欲绝
Why aren't you devastated?
泰迪  大家开始围观了
Teddy, people are staring.
噢
Oh ho ho,
看来我让你难堪了
So I'm embarrassing you?
不对  不对  你本应该让我难堪的  小伙
No no, you're supposed to be embarrassing me, fella.
-哇  哇  -初次分手  大家见笑了
-Whoa whoa! -First breakup, people.
噢  等着  分手仪式还未结束
Oh no, this breakup's not over!
我一会儿会给你打电话的
I'm calling you later!
这是你最后的一张工资支票
Here is your last check.
以后别联系
Do not stay in touch.
我一直讨厌你
I never liked you.
立正
Atten-hut!
布尔·咕唧下士前来报到
Corporal bull s. Kwikki is in the corral.
-你怎么来了  -借过  朋友
-What are you doing here? -Excuse me, pardner.
我听说这里存在着长期不和
I heard there was some feuding going on down here.
根据经营法第157条
At franchise 157.
劳资纠纷
Labor dispute.
恕我直言  下士
May I say, corporal,
呃  我看着您真人的体型偏大啊
Um, you look somewhat bigger in person.
呃  没错
Uh, yes.
那个  促销部
Well, the promotional department.
认为我缩水成这样后
Thinks I'm more relatable to the peoples.
更能带给顾客一种可靠度
When I'm all shrunk down like that.
让我来问问你  下士
Let me ask you, corporal,
你到底从哪里来
Where exactly did you come from?
噢  从那边
Oh, out yonder.
你说的那个那边
And exactly which state.
到底在哪个州呢
Is yonder in?
先生  那就是  呃
Sir, that would be the great state of, uh...
阿拉巴马州
Alabama?
回答错误  大家都知道布尔·咕唧下士
Wrong! Everyone knows corporal bull s. Kwikki.
来自新泽西州
Is from new Jersey.
-疼啊  -这个骗子到底是谁
-Ow. -Who is this imposter?
好了  我可以解释
Okay, I can explain.
这里究竟又出什么乱子了
What in tarnation is going on in here?
难以置信  这才是真正的布尔·咕唧下士
I don't believe it! This is the real corporal kwikki!
别闹了  你觉着我有多傻
Come on, how stupid do you think I am?
我才不是来自新泽西州的那个
I did not come all the way from the great state of new Jersey.
假胡子被拽掉的巨人
To have my beard yanked by a troll.
亲娘咧  现真身了
Oh my goodness, it really is you.
咕唧下士  荣幸啊  先生
Corporal kwikki, it's an honor, sir.
别光耍嘴皮子了  伙计
Quit flapping your gums, boy,
快点把这些孩子的工作还回来
And give these kids their jobs back.
还要支付我们应得的工资  底薪
And pay us what we deserve... minimum wage!
没问题  小意思
Done and done.
现在快去给我端上来点油炸卷
Now go wrassle me up some Curly fries.
我的饥肠辘辘也就只有
I got a powerful hunger that can only be satisfied.
油炸卷可以满足
By the curliest of fries.
我表现的还可以吗  PJ  是不是
How did I do, P.J? Was it...
克恩先生  演得太绝了  太谢谢您了
Mr. Kern, that was awesome. Thank you so much.
等一下  克恩先生不是你的工艺课老师吗
Wait a minute. Mr. Kern your shop teacher?
是的
Yeah.
我一直想当个戏剧老师  你觉着我怎么样
I'm trying to become the drama teacher. How do you think I did?
-我觉着我有这个能力  -噢  绝了
-'cause I think I nailed it. -Oh, it was awesome.
大家好  布尔·咕唧下士来也
Howdy, y'all. Bull s. Kwikki here.
老爸  你来迟了
Dad, you're late.
我们都演完了
We got it covered.
搞什么飞机  我上班请假就为了这个
For crying out loud! I took off work for this?
嘿  查莉  听着  没有多少时间了
Hey, Charlie, listen, don't have a lot of time.
马上去找德里克  我们还在分手仪式中
Gotta go meet Derek. We're still breaking up.
是啊  是啊  你懂的
Yeah yeah, you know,
我们只是  我们会持续分手下去的
We'll just... we'll continue to break up.
直到他正确应对此事
Until he gets it right.
老妈  快走了  我们会比赛迟到的
Mom, let's go. We're gonna be late for my game.
好的  好的  我带了  派阳镜
Okay okay okay, I have my thun-glathes,
钥系  咸包  我还忘泰什么了
My keyth, my purthe. What am I mithing?
牙
Your teeth.
那是谁的蛇任啊
And who'th responthible for that?
抱献了
<i>Thorry.</i>
嘿  别这么和我奢话  先生
Hey, don't you <i>thath</i> me, mister.
看来  在这个家里
Well, in this house.
真是趣事不断啊
It's always something.
嘿  删别录呢
Hey, don't <i>you</i> thtart!
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
噢  我断言  她比鸭屁股更可爱
Aw, I declare, she is cuter than a duck's butt.
好了  希望你们这帮伙计肚子饿了
Well, I hope you boys is hungry.
我老婆搞到了一些食物
The missus is rustling up some grub.
就是没有鸡肉  小伙子
Anything but chicken, son.
演得不错  先生  演的不错啊
Well played, sir. Well played.
好了  在我们等待的同时  不如来唱支歌吧
Well, while we're waiting, how about a song?
好主意
That's a fine idea.
你会雷迪·嘎嘎的歌吗
Do you know any lady gaga?
就唱“牧场是我家”
"home on the range" it is.
哦  给我一个家
Oh, give me a home
那里水牛漫步
Where the Buffalo roam
那里小鹿羚羊嬉戏
And the deer and the antelope play
辣里从未听到
Where theldom is heard
半句气馁的发
A dithcouragin' word
只有停空万里  咿
And the thkies are not cloudy all day-eee!
别妄想了  先生们
Back off, gentlemen,
这位无牙美女是我的
That toothless darling's all mine.